alright next stop and in that Carolyn
villa ok that's separated for not going
to come up here dr. it for ample hotter
was herself except that it's Anna
clearly international home treatment do
not support teeth she's a physician a
clinical neurologist and a neural
physiologist okay she serves her as yes
sir as a gaby number in case I had a
global health in the med school of
medicine remember the board of directors
the directors of the Clinton Foundation
a member of mental health objection
board chair of the international
appearance in services Canadian a
Cleveland Red Cross the advisory board
of the cleveland institute of art and a
helmet lost cancer research foundation
and i think a wide breaking paulina
lucky too because you remember for 2014
her list is long and i talked about yet
she is president and designer of various
designs of fine fashion jewelry line
that i would probable roman emperor of
pieces so i'd like to introduce dr.
maria cahaba cooling duct para bailar